okay so I think it's time to get the
好吧，我认为现在是时候
show on the road
在路上展示
thanks for showing up when to load up
感谢您显示何时加载
testing today's topic is of course Jane
测试今天的话题当然是简
at five and new opportunities were
在五个，新的机会是
testing on the JVM my name is Sam
在JVM上测试我叫Sam
Brannan I'm a spring and Java
布兰南我是Java的春天
consultants at a company called Swift
一家名为Swift的公司的顾问
mine in Zurich Switzerland trainer coach
瑞士苏黎世的矿山教练教练
etc but a hard co-developer at heart
等，但是内心很努力
I've been a job developer for about
我曾经是约
twenty years
20年
course spring vagrant commuter since
自从春季游民通勤以来
2007 which when I originally I'm rewrote
2007年，当我最初重写时
Springs testing support of the whole
整体的弹簧测试支持
annotation based stuff support for
基于注释的东西支持
testing GJ and for etc and I've been a
测试GJ和for etc，我一直
core committer for j25 since October
自10月以来，j25的核心提交者
2015 so Swift mine experts in spring and
Swift矿山专家在2015年春季和
Java you can find us online if you want
Java您可以在网上找到我们
some consulting on how to use deign to
一些关于如何使用设计的咨询
five better perhaps spring etc so the
五个更好的也许春天等所以
agenda for us to talk about impetus for
我们谈论推动动力的议程
change like why we did it
像我们为什么那样改变
then I'll talk about Jane at five in
那我五点钟谈简
detail a little bit about spring five
详细介绍春季五
and then time permitting Q&amp;A though if
然后如果有时间允许进行问答
you're unhappy with the 45-minute format
您对45分钟的格式不满意
as I've heard other speakers say then
就像我听到其他发言者说的那样
feel free to complain it would be nice
随时抱怨这会很好
if we had an hour unfortunately we got
如果不幸的是我们有一个小时
to rush it through for 45 minutes but no
赶了45分钟但没有
fear we have AB off tonight on Jane of
担心我们今晚要在简的
five so if they're more questions and
五，如果他们还有更多问题，
stuff like that if you want to see me
如果你想见我的话
live code some more stuff here answers
现场代码更多的东西在这里答案
more questions then please come to the
还有更多问题，请到
to the buff as well that would be great
也会很好
so first up show of hands who writes
所以先写出谁写的手
tests all right
测试没事
who uses a J unit anyone okay anyone use
谁使用J单位谁可以使用任何人
anything other than Janet yes
除了珍妮特以外，是的
testing G maybe 2% a Spock something
测试G也许是Spock的2％
like that a few more any kind of other
像其他一些
like scholar tests or anything else I
像是学者考试或其他任何东西
have no one guy okay so everyone Java
没有人可以，所以每个人都Java
Java Jane it I didn't ask the Virgin
Java Jane我没问过维珍
Jane it for I suppose right anyone still
简，因为我想对任何人都还对
using Jane at three oh you sorry sorry
三点钟使用简哦，对不起，对不起
Souls or so as well we've got we've got
灵魂也是如此，我们有我们有
you covered actually so why do we have a
你实际上涵盖了，为什么我们有一个
new version of Jane it if your
简的新版本，如果您的
experience with Jane it and you've tried
经历过简，而你已经尝试过
implement stuff on you and you might
在你身上实施东西，你可能
know some of the reasons but just over
知道一些原因，但刚刚结束
you for those who don't know
对于那些不知道的人
so Jane for was released over a decade
所以珍妮被释放了十多年
ago a lot has changed since then our
从那以后，我们发生了很多变化
testing needs as the community have
测试社区的需求
mature
成熟
and our expectations have grown from we
和我们的期望已经增长
expect from her framework so I often say
从她的框架中期望，所以我经常说
J dude is a horrible name because it has
J dude是个可怕的名字，因为它有
the word unit baked into it and people
单词单元融入其中，人们
think it's only about unit testing but
认为这仅与单元测试有关
obviously that's not the case anymore
显然现在已经不是了
right integration testing system testing
正确的集成测试系统测试
intends testing all sorts of stuff
打算测试各种东西
another thing with Jana four terms of
贾纳（Jana）的另外四件事
modularity they're really um wasn't much
他们实际上是模块化的，数量不多
right kind of a big ball of mud there
那里有种大泥球
was only the Janet jar right and disk on
只是珍妮特罐子和磁盘上
test discovery and execution those
测试发现并执行那些
issues were tightly coupled
问题紧密耦合
extensibility a lot of room for
扩展性很大的空间
improvement there and we hopefully have
那里的改善，我们希望有
achieved that and last but not least
实现了这一点，但最后但并非最不重要的一点
let's not forget about modern versions
让我们不要忘记现代版本
of the JVM right so we have Java 8 and
JVM的正确性，所以我们有Java 8和
even Java 9 and of course Jana for only
甚至Java 9，当然也只有Jana
theoretically supports Java 5 so to
理论上支持Java 5，因此
speak in terms of the API so in Jana 4
用API来表达，所以在Jana 4中
there's this main concept of a
这是一个主要的概念
runner-runner api it's very powerful in
跑步者api的功能非常强大
fact you can do anything can do name
其实你可以做任何可以做的事
with it but you can't combine runners so
它，但您不能合并跑步者，所以
for example if you ever try to use the
例如，如果您尝试使用
parameterize runner from jane unit and
参数化来自简单位的跑步者和
the spring runner from spring it's a
春天的春天赛跑者
no-go doesn't work right something in
不行对某事不起作用
the next slide we have here is a bit of
我们在这里的下一张幻灯片有点
a joke so um you might think je given
这么开玩笑，你可能会以为
for rules like super cool or you might
对于超酷的规则，否则您可能会
read it as rules are meant to be broken
阅读它，因为规则注定要被打破
and I would say for rules are meant to
我想说规则是为了
be broken and in fact always were
被打破，实际上总是
unfortunately so in Jaden 47 there was
不幸的是，在贾登47
this method rule you can annotates up
您可以注释此方法规则
with that rule and have that registered
遵守该规则并进行注册
then they came up with an idea for a
然后他们想出了一个
class level support with test drill and
带有测试演练的班级支持和
Jana 4/9 you could have it at the kind
Jana 4/9您可以善加利用
of like the method level or the class
像方法级别或类
level and that's great for simple use
水平，这很容易使用
cases they can even be combined which is
他们甚至可以结合在一起的情况是
which is nice but it's single rule can't
很好，但这是单条规则
to be used for both method level and
用于方法级别和
class level callbacks plus there's zero
类级别的回调加零
support for what I call instance level
支持我所谓的实例级别
callbacks so case in point if you've
回调，例如
ever used the spring support with rules
曾经使用过弹簧支撑和规则
I had to implement this as two rules
我必须将其作为两个规则实施
unfortunately so it's pretty ugly
不幸的是，这很丑陋
boilerplate code you have to say you
您必须说出样板代码
want the spring class rule and the
想要春季班规则和
spring method rule where you really just
弹簧方法规则
want to say I just want spring right so
想说我只想要春天吧
what happened how did this all come
发生了什么事
about that we got to Jane to five first
关于我们，我们先到了简五
we had a crowdfunding campaign called
我们开展了一项名为
Jane at lambda
简·兰达
people - listed here as one of the main
人员-在这里列为主要人员之一
sponsors they're initiated by some some
他们是由一些人发起的
German guys previous committers on Jane
德国人以前对简的提交者
at four joined by some other German guys
四岁时还有其他一些德国人加入
and and
和
yours truly we all happen to speak
真的，我们所有人都在说话
German which is just kind of a
德国人只是一种
coincidence I don't know maybe it's just
巧合，我不知道可能只是
because Germans like to test perhaps I
因为德国人喜欢测试我
don't know and our latest committer is
不知道，我们最新的提交者是
also from Germany so yeah we need some
也是德国的，所以我们需要一些
people from like the states in other
来自其他州的人们
countries maybe anyway so this ran from
国家，无论如何，所以这是从
July to October 2015
2015年7月至10月
raised a fair amount of money and for
筹集了很多钱
companies located donated six weeks of
所在公司捐赠了六周的
full-time developer time including a
专职开发人员时间，包括
pill - who also contributed more so
药-谁也贡献了更多
pivotal not just spring also supporting
关键不仅是弹簧还支持
the the June 5 initiative so if your
6月5日的倡议，因此，如果您
names up here or your company then thank
在这里命名或您的公司，然后谢谢
you very much for helping us get started
非常感谢您帮助我们入门
what that helps us do it helped us have
什么可以帮助我们做到这一点帮助我们
a kickoff meeting we have some big names
开工会议，我们有一些知名人士
in the community developer from Gradle
在Gradle的社区开发人员中
Ellijay and clips as well as these core
Ellijay和剪辑以及这些核心
committers coming together we started
提交者聚集在一起，我们开始了
off and kicked off J and 5 so first off
开球，J和5开始，所以首先
we had a prototype we did back released
我们有一个原型，我们做了回发行
in December 2015 then we had an alpha a
在2015年12月，我们有了一个alpha
few months later and then huge big step
几个月后又迈出了一大步
to the m1 couple milestones in between
到介于两者之间的m1里程碑
over a course of a year couple releases
一年多的时间，情侣发布
to Canada is I say 2 to 3 because the
去加拿大是说2到3，因为
first one was kind of snafu didn't
第一个是snafu没有
really exist so we really had to that
确实存在，所以我们真的不得不
you could use and then 5 that Ogier so
您可以使用然后5个Ogier这样
hopefully you heard about that
希望你听说过
September 10th 2017 and as of today a
2017年9月10日至今
few hours ago we released 501 so with a
几个小时前，我们发布了501，
few small bug fixes in case you're ready
一些小错误修复，以防万一您准备好了
on on 5 oh so that's where we are
继续5哦，那是我们的位置
chained to 5 in a nutshell it's modular
简而言之，链接到5个是模块化的
right so we have lots of modules you'll
对，所以我们有很多模块
see that it's very extensible and we
看到它非常可扩展，我们
like to think it's modern right it silly
喜欢认为它是现代的，很愚蠢
string in Java 8 and has some modern
Java 8中的字符串，并具有一些现代
features like land expressions and stuff
土地表达和事物之类的功能
like that another really crucial thing
像那样，另一个非常关键的事情
that we put a lot of consideration to is
我们很多考虑的是
is compatibility being both forward and
兼容性既向前又
backward compatible at the same time so
同时向后兼容
what that means is that the junior
那意味着初中
platform which I'll talk about in a
平台，我将在
minute that supports on Jana 3/8 and and
分钟支持Jana 3/8和
at the same time as what we would call
与我们所说的同时
Jana 5 or the new Jupiter programming
Jana 5或新的Jupiter编程
model in addition new testing frameworks
模型以及新的测试框架
that are based on the platform can be
基于平台的可以
run with Jana port infrastructure so
与Jana港口基础设施一起运行，因此
that means you can use your old IDs and
这意味着您可以使用旧的ID和
your old bill tools if you want to but
您的旧账单工具，如果您想
we'll see we're getting support for
我们将看到我们正在获得支持
build tools and ideas along the way so
在此过程中建立工具和想法
the way this is done with fuel every
每次使用燃油的方式
chain of on a particular runner for the
特定跑步者的链
platform
平台
called Jane to platform so you just say
叫简到平台，所以你只说
I run with Jane a platform you can run
我与简一起运行一个可以运行的平台
that in an old version of Eclipse old
在旧版本的Eclipse中
version NetBeans IntelliJ etc so in
NetBeans IntelliJ等版本
terms of um version support obviously
um版本支持的条款显然
job eight right otherwise it wouldn't be
工作八对吧，否则就不会
modern that's the baseline right so it's
现代是基线的权利，所以
all compiled in Java 8 using lemon
全部使用柠檬在Java 8中编译
expressions stuff like that but you
这样的表情，但是你
could of course use it to test the
当然可以用它来测试
application code compiled against the
应用程序代码针对
previous version right a different
以前的版本不一样
target version Java 9 version also
目标版本Java 9版本也
supported all right you might have seen
支持您可能已经看到的所有权利
in keynote Mark had all those open
在主题演讲中，马克将所有评论都公开了
source projects in set up there and on
在那里建立源代码项目
Jane of 5 is in fact one of them works
5岁的简实际上就是其中一位
fine on JDK 9 and if each of the
在JDK 9上很好，如果每个
artifacts has a stable automatic module
文物具有稳定的自动模块
name our unit so you can already use it
为我们的单位命名，以便您可以使用它
on the module path if you choose to and
如果您选择并在模块路径上
we'll support for scanning the module
我们将支持扫描模块
path for your test classes and stuff
测试课程和内容的路径
like that in 5.1 that's the plan so
像5.1这样的计划
right now we have class path scan and
现在我们有类路径扫描和
support and we'll add module path and
支持，我们将添加模块路径和
skin and support as well so this this is
皮肤和支撑，所以这是
very key I'll say a few times there is
非常关键，我会说几次
no spoon right ok there is no J unit 5
没有勺子好吧没有J单元5
you can't say I have Jane at 4 and
你不能说我四岁时有简
change the version to 5 it's not going
将版本更改为5不会
to work because we actually rewrote
工作，因为我们实际上重写了
everything and we actually in the
一切，我们实际上在
process ended up inventing three kind of
过程最终发明了三种
projects together we didn't realize at
我们一起没有意识到的项目
the start but after a while we realized
开始，但一段时间后，我们意识到
and split it up and we gave them names
并分开，我们给他们起名字
so we have the Jaina platform released
所以我们发布了Jaina平台
at version 1.0 that's the foundation for
在1.0版中，这是
launching your testing framework on the
在...上启动测试框架
JVM and I say any testing framerate
JVM，我说任何测试帧率
doesn't mean it has to be in Java
并不意味着它必须使用Java
doesn't mean it has to be from the JV
并不意味着一定要来自合资企业
team
球队
it could be Scala groovy Kotlin whatever
可能是Scala groovy Kotlin
you can own so for that we have what are
您可以拥有，因此我们拥有
known as the launcher and test engine
被称为启动器和测试引擎
API is we have them built in a console
API是我们将它们内置在控制台中
launcher built-in support for Gradle and
启动器内置对Gradle和
maven and then the next part is what you
专家，然后下一部分就是你
might actually consider to be J unit 5
可能实际上认为是J单元5
it's the new programming model and
这是新的编程模型，
extension model that you'll be using
您将使用的扩展模型
mainly if you're you're focusing on on J
主要是如果您专注于J
units right so this is called Jana
正确的单位，因此称为Jana
Jupiter a lot of people ask why Jupiter
木星很多人问为什么木星
what's the fifth planet from the Sun
太阳的第五颗行星是什么
Jupiter it happens to also start with J
木星碰巧也以J开头
you like J unit so that's kind of cool
你喜欢J unit，所以很酷
too all right
太好了
you could say j-unit Jupiter if you want
你可以说j单位木星
to pronounce it like that okay so next
像这样发音，所以接下来
part we toss it on some ideas out legacy
部分，我们将其遗留在一些想法上
um the people we thought may be filled
嗯，我们认为可能会被填补的人
feel insulted so I said maybe maybe
感到侮辱，所以我说也许
retro when they decide the vintage is a
当他们决定年份是复古时
support for what came before and that
支持以前发生的事情
means we have a test engine that will
意味着我们有一个测试引擎
support running Jane III if you're so
如果可以，则支持运行Jane III
unfortunate but also Jane at four at the
不幸的是，简也四点钟
same time and actually we didn't aim to
同时，实际上我们并非旨在
support Jane you three just happens to
支持简，你三个刚好碰巧
be the Jane at four supports two three
简在四点支持两个三
so we couldn't not support any three in
所以我们不能支持任何三个
that regard so so it is and then some
那个方面是这样，然后一些
some points here very important so the
这里有些要点很重要，所以
first part is is revolutionary right
第一部分是革命权利
this is never really existed before the
这从来没有真正存在过
platform really is a new platform to
平台真的是一个新的平台
write any kind of testing framework that
编写任何类型的测试框架
runs on the JVM and everyone can benefit
在JVM上运行，每个人都可以受益
from that you can put in testing framers
由此您可以放入测试成帧器
and stuff the next one is evolutionary
接下来的东西是进化的
right so there was genuine for and now
对，所以现在有货真价实
there's this Jane at Jupiter kind of
木星有这个简
Jane to five but similar program models
简至五个但相似的程序模型
just just kind of evolutionary and the
只是一种进化而已
last part I would say is necessary just
我要说的最后一部分是必要的
to support existing uh testing code
支持现有的呃测试代码
bases so this launcher API like Jane at
因此，像Jane这样的启动器API
core and Jane Fortran or that it's used
core和Jane Fortran或已使用
by IDs and tools to launch the framework
通过ID和启动框架的工具
so you wouldn't probably use it yourself
所以你自己可能不会用
but you could if you wanted to play
但是如果你想玩就可以
around with it and it's essential API
它是基本的API
for discovering and executing tests via
用于通过发现和执行测试
one or more registered test engines and
一个或多个注册的测试引擎，以及
for that there's what's known as a
为此，有一个所谓的
launcher discovery request has support
启动器发现请求具有支持
for what we call selectors and filters
我们称之为选择器和过滤器
selectors you can select things like
选择器，您可以选择类似
select this uh from the class path this
从课程路径中选择这个
class path routes you can select
您可以选择的班级路径路线
packages to scan you can select tests
要扫描的软件包可以选择测试
classes for example you can also select
例如，您还可以选择
individual test methods these kind of
个别测试方法
things and filtering you can filter
可以过滤的东西和过滤
based on like um test engine IDs or
根据类似um测试引擎ID或
filter based on class names like that
根据这样的类名进行过滤
you know like a pattern for the class or
你知道像上课的模式
tags and stuff like that so a lot
标签和类似的东西很多
Beacher's actually aren't supported ed
实际上不支持Beacher的版本
in the IDE but we think that will come
在IDE中，但我们认为这将会实现
with time terms of getting feedback if
有时间获得反馈的条件，如果
you want to have your own tie into the
您想拥有自己的领带
reporting infrastructure you could
报告您可以的基础架构
implement a text execution listener and
实现一个文本执行监听器，并
get get feedback on all the events that
获取有关所有事件的反馈
are occurring as the test plan execute
在执行测试计划时发生
and then again this console launcher
然后再次是这个控制台启动器
allows you to actually run on the test
允许您实际运行测试
suite from the console if you wanted to
如果需要，可以从控制台进行设置
or run it from a Java main or something
或从Java main之类运行它
else like that
像那样
so test engine API you might consider
因此，您可能会考虑测试引擎API
this someone analogous to the runner API
这个类似于跑步者API的人
from Jane for accepted the test engine
来自Jane接受测试引擎
API is generic and not limited to Java
API是通用的，不限于Java
per se so a test engine discovers and
本身，因此测试引擎会发现并
executes tests key here for a particular
在这里执行特定测试键
programming model and these things can
编程模型，这些东西可以
be automatically registered with the
被自动注册到
Java service layer mechanism so as long
Java服务层机制这么久
as they have the right information there
因为他们在那里有正确的信息
in the jar and they're on the class path
在罐子里，他们在上课的路上
and they get automatically registered
他们会自动注册
which is cool right and for Jana Jupiter
对Jana Jupiter来说很酷
we have a Jupiter test engine then to
我们有一个木星测试引擎，然后
vintage we have one as well and you can
年份我们也有一个，你可以
implement your own which people have
实现自己拥有的人
actually done so this is taken straight
实际这样做，这是直截了当的
from this page we have a wiki page we
从这个页面我们有一个维基页面，我们
allow people to publish their posts
允许人们发布他们的帖子
third-party extensions they've written
他们编写的第三方扩展
for the giant platform or Gianna Jupiter
用于巨型平台或Gianna Jupiter
and we can see at least five that I know
我们至少可以看到五个
of existing test engines outside of the
现有的外部测试引擎
two I mentioned that come from the giant
我提到的两个来自巨人
team itself so for example like this
团队本身，例如这样
specs one at the top some guy grid is on
在顶部列出一些家伙网格
a little testing framework based on
一些基于的测试框架
closures and stuff like that and it
闭包之类的东西
works in Scala Java and groovy the spec
可在Scala Java中工作并遵循规范
one is for Kotlin and yep you can check
一个是给科特林的，是的，你可以检查一下
out the others if you want as well so
如果需要的话也可以排除其他人
here's the the big picture because
这是全局，因为
people like big pictures right so here
人们喜欢大图片，所以在这里
we have the platform in the middle right
我们在右中间有平台
and some inter for the IDs and build
和一些除了ID和建立
tools we use that and what you do you're
我们使用的工具以及您所从事的工作
up at the top you're gonna writing your
在顶部，你要写你的
old test change of core stuff like that
像这样的核心材料的旧测试更改
it will use the vintage infrastructure
它将使用老式的基础设施
if you're using Jaina Jupiter we using
如果您使用的是吉安娜·朱庇特，我们会使用
that infrastructure or one of these
该基础架构或其中之一
third-party test engines like I mention
我提到的第三方测试引擎
on the previous slide or if you write
在上一张幻灯片上，或者如果您写
your own and then everything else is the
你自己的，然后其他一切都是
platform the middle so if you look
平台中间，所以如果你看
behind the scenes there we'll see the
在幕后，我们将看到
old test is just using JUnit 4 12 right
旧的测试只是使用JUnit 4 12对
and we have this Jane at vintage engine
我们在老式引擎上有这个简
that knows how to adapt from Jane at 4
知道如何适应4岁时的Jane
to the platform test engine API and then
到平台测试引擎API，然后
we have the new stuff the Jupiter API
我们有新的东西Jupiter API
that's what you code against and the
这就是您针对的代码，
engine is what supports it and then
引擎是什么支持它，然后
every other third-party would have their
其他所有第三方都有
own API in their own engine invitation
在自己的引擎邀请中拥有自己的API
as well and then and then internally
以及然后然后内部
right so the IDs they're gonna work with
对，所以他们要使用的ID
this this launcher and we have different
这个这个发射器，我们有不同
things that run that so that runner I've
跑着跑的东西
talked about for Jana for that's in
为Jana谈论，因为
there we got the Surefire support the
在那里，我们得到了Surefire的支持
Gradle support and the console launcher
Gradle支持和控制台启动器
all talking to the same API so this is
所有人都在使用相同的API，所以这是
what I'm saying that it's new
我说的是新的
opportunities for the JVM and we talked
JVM的机会，我们谈到了
about Jane at 5 if we would focus on
如果我们专注于5点左右的简
that right that's just just this little
那个权利就这么少
green part
绿色部分
up here and everything else is more like
在这里，其他一切都更像
the platform right and anyone else can
平台权利，其他任何人都可以
implement their own stuff so that's why
实现自己的东西，这就是为什么
I say it's a it's a game changer
我说这是一个改变游戏规则的人
so terms of ID and build support
因此，ID和构建支持条款
IntelliJ has been supporting us for
IntelliJ一直在支持我们
quite a long time so as I mentioned we
很长一段时间，所以正如我提到的
had one of the core developers that came
有一位核心开发者
to our kickoff meeting and we've been
参加我们的启动会议，我们一直
communicating with her ever since then
从那时起与她沟通
so ever since idea 2016 2 and above
自从Idea 2016 2以上
they've had support and they have
他们有支持，他们有
support for a ga recently as well
最近也支持ga
Eclipse joined the game a little bit
Eclipse有点加入了游戏
later but they have actually very good
后来，但他们实际上非常好
support eclipse auction 4.7 that one a
支持日食拍卖4.7那一个
is supposed to be released next week on
应该在下周发布
the 11th I think or something like that
我认为是第11个
and it's actually I'm using the release
而实际上我正在使用发行版
candidate one for that in the demos
演示中的候选人之一
today
今天
NetBeans I think the the monkeys tell
我认为猴子说的是NetBeans
the story I'll leave it at that
这个故事我会留在那
Gradle we have an interim solution from
Gradle我们有一个临时解决方案
the data team we've written ourselves we
我们自己编写的数据团队
are not experts in Gradle or in writing
不是Gradle或写作方面的专家
Gradle plugins we wrote one and it works
我们写了一个Gradle插件就可以了
and we use it ourselves and the Gradle
我们自己使用它和Gradle
team is going to be taking that over
团队将接管
time permitting hopefully by the end of
希望在年底之前有时间
this year they've claimed recently on
今年，他们最近宣称
issue tracker
问题追踪器
there's also third-party support for
还有第三方支持
Android the nice gentleman from the
Android的好绅士
community has written so you can check
社区已撰写，因此您可以检查
that out if you need to work with Jane
如果您需要与简一起工作
at 5:00 and Android maven we also have
在5:00和Android Maven，我们也有
an interim solution there that we've
我们有一个临时解决方案
used an implanted and that's currently
使用了植入物，目前
being taken over by the maven a surefire
被行家接管了
team so we donated the code that we have
团队，所以我们捐赠了我们拥有的代码
in there take forward from there that's
从那里前进
the idea and we have no ant support we
这个想法，我们没有蚂蚁的支持，我们
have an open issue grabs if you want to
有一个开放的问题，如果你想
implement it feel free in terms of how
在如何实现方面感到自由
to set the stuff up I'm not going to
设置东西我不会
time to show it today so if you want to
时间今天展示，所以如果你想
see how just take out the user guide for
看看如何取出用户指南
documentation we also some sample sample
文档我们也提供一些样本
apps that show you how to get Gradle and
展示如何获取Gradle和
maven up and running with the platform
使用平台进行Maven运行
itself and with Jana Jupiter or with
本身以及与Jana Jupiter或与
Jana advantage as well so now we're
贾娜（Jana）也有优势，所以现在我们
going to jump into Jana I'm gonna give
要跳进贾娜，我要给
you an overview of the extension model
您对扩展模型的概述
and if you have more questions we can
如果您还有其他问题，我们可以
talk about that during the Boff tonight
今晚在Boff谈论
so we have an extension that's marker
所以我们有一个扩展是标记
interface it word Jane at Jupiter API
在Jupiter API上将它与Jane界面
extension packages are different from we
扩展程序包与我们不同
had in Jane at Fort Wright so there are
曾在赖特堡的简中，所以有
any conflicts that was also a design
任何冲突也是设计
decision there and yep limit as many as
那里的决定和是限制
you like right so I said you couldn't
你喜欢对，所以我说你不能
combine rules
结合规则
or you couldn't have a class level than
否则你的课程水平不能超过
a method level rule Jana 4 and Jana
方法级别规则Jana 4和Jana
Jupiter you can combine them as you wish
木星，您可以根据需要将它们组合
and the way you register one of those
以及您注册其中之一的方式
instead of run with in j2 40s at extend
而不是在j2 40s中运行
with and they specify one or more who
并指定一个或多个
sent you to be registered at the class
派你去上课
level method level or the first we're
级别方法级别或第一个
there even on interfaces right so that's
甚至在正确的接口上，所以
kind of cool
有点酷
even on interface default methods and
即使在接口默认方法上
stuff like that as well so or right ok
这样的东西也好吧
who's ever used spring anyone yep and
谁曾经用过弹簧？
you know meta annotation support cool
你知道元注释支持很酷
annotation support so in Jana five I put
注释支持，所以我在Jana 5中放了
really hard to convince the team that so
真的很难说服团队
we support
我们支持
it's a meta annotation this working
这是一个元注释，可以正常工作
about anything am i doing something
关于我在做什么
wrong
错误
no flailing I'll stop flailing extension
没有，我将停止扩展
API is so here we have before all before
API就是这里
each we have befores and afters for
每个我们之前和之后的
various levels so all is a class level
各个级别，所以都是一个班级
that we like before class before each
我们喜欢上课前
would be like kind of before in Gen 4
就像第四代之前的那种
and before test execution this is
在执行测试之前，这是
immediately before the test methods
测试方法之前
executed or mealy afterwards and these
之后被处决或吃饭
are what's known as lifecycle callbacks
是所谓的生命周期回调
but these are the extensions right so
但是这些是扩展名，所以
the extensions map on to the user
扩展映射到用户
extension points as well beyond that we
扩展点以及超越我们
have something comes kinda in the middle
中间有些东西
there right after the methods executed
方法执行完之后
there is a test execution exception
有一个测试执行异常
handler which allows you to handle
允许您处理的处理程序
exceptions if you wanted to implement
异常，如果你想实现
something like an expected ception or
诸如预期的感受或
logging exceptions and stuff like that
记录异常之类的东西
another thing we have it's called
我们有另一件事叫做
execution condition talk about more in
执行条件更多讨论
detail in a bit test instance post
测试实例文章中的详细信息
processor and parameter resolver very
处理器和参数解析器
cool and this is the support for
很酷，这是对
dependency injection in j-unit Jupiter
j单位木星中的依赖注入
so much better than what we had in Jade
比我们翡翠的好多了
for and the last one a bit more complex
对于最后一个要复杂一点
we have a test template invocation
我们有一个测试模板调用
context provider and that's we're doing
上下文提供者，这就是我们正在做的
cool stuff like repeated test
很酷的东西，例如反复测试
parametrize test test matrices and stuff
参数测试测试矩阵和东西
like that so now the programming model
这样，现在编程模型
what you'll use the most all these
您将最常使用的是什么
things are located in the org Jane
东西位于组织简中
Jupiter API package so they're not in
Jupiter API程序包，因此它们不在
org Jane it right don't get confused and
简，请不要混淆，
pick the wrong test annotation and if
选择错误的测试注释，如果
you're using the parameter support
您正在使用参数支持
that's in a prams package if using the
如果使用
jane to for Migration support we'll see
简支持迁移，我们将看到
you later that's also in a different
你以后也有不同
pack but most of the stuff is in this
包装，但大多数东西是在
api package so roll
api包所以滚
feature-set we support annotations and
功能集我们支持注释和
swear there was a net annotations we
发誓我们有一个网络注释
have assertions and assumptions custom
有断言和假设习惯
display names visibility not everything
显示名称可见性不是全部
has to be public anymore so you can type
必须再公开，所以您可以输入
plus we have built-in support for
再加上我们对
tagging conditional test execution
标记条件测试执行
dependency injection both for
依赖注入都
constructors and methods we support
我们支持的构造函数和方法
lambda expressions and methods in
Lambda表达式和方法
various places for example in assertions
各个地方，例如断言
and stuff like that we allow you to use
和类似的东西，我们允许您使用
the fault methods job eight things like
故障方法可以完成八件事
that new nested tests class support and
新的嵌套测试类支持
then also repeated tests permanence
然后还要反复测试永久性
chests and dynamic tests so in terms of
胸部和动态测试，因此
annotations these are the main ones at
这些是主要的注释
test we couldn't come up with a better
测试我们无法提出更好的
name so we left it the same for dynamic
名称，因此我们将其保留为动态
tests we we have test factory and in
测试我们有测试工厂
gray here is that testable so if you're
灰色是可以测试的，所以如果你是
writing a test engine you would actually
编写一个您实际上会使用的测试引擎
want to use that annotation
想要使用该注释
next up variations of tests so we have
接下来的测试变化，所以我们有
repeated tests and parameterize tests
重复测试并参数化测试
and these are specializations or what's
这些是专长还是什么
known as a test template as I mentioned
我提到的称为测试模板
previously before nested tests classes
之前在嵌套测试类之前
at tes instance so I'm going to make a
在tes实例上，所以我要做一个
statement and you can see who actually
声明，您可以看到实际上是谁
knows this
知道这个
so in JUnit one through four Jane it
所以在JUnit一到四个Jane中
always reinstates your test class
总是恢复您的测试课程
between every test method who knew that
知道的每种测试方法之间
so maybe 10% right and intestine G its
所以大约有10％的肠道G
exact opposite it keeps your testing
正好相反，它可以保持您的测试
since the entire time so I've often been
因为一直以来，我经常
a fan of the weight testing G does it
重量测试G的粉丝做到了
and I had this in the prototype and then
我在原型中有这个，然后
got voted out but I got it voted back in
被投票但我被投票回
and reimplemented it for TA
并为TA重新实现
so in Janet Jupiter you can pick the
所以在珍妮特·朱庇特，你可以选择
model you want you can say I want to
您想要的模特可以说我想要
have pistons as per class or per method
根据类别或方法安装活塞
and one of the reasons that I was able
这也是我之所以能够做到的原因之一
to convince the team is because it's
说服团队是因为
actually pre good cause it for
其实预先做好是因为
supporting things like scenario tests
支持场景测试
which we want to support in a later
我们希望在以后支持
release so we have before all after all
释放，所以我们毕竟拥有
that's like before class and after class
就像上课之前和课后一样
before each and after each that's like
在每个之前和之后，就像
before and after display name
显示名称之前和之后
that's where customs play name tags that
那是海关打名字标签的地方
kind of replaces categories in Jana for
种替换Jana中的类别以
and now disabled replaces at ignore
现在禁用替换为忽略
people say why didn't you keep it well
人们说你为什么不把它保持好
it'll make more sense when I talk about
当我谈论这件事时会更有意义
the execution stuff in a bit but
执行的东西，但
basically I couldn't come up with an
基本上我无法提出
opposite of ignore because we do not
与忽略相反，因为我们不
ignore it is not ignored and it makes
忽略它不被忽略，它使
more sense to say a test is either
说测试更有意义
enabled or disabled and that comes
启用或禁用，并且
through and the API will see later on so
通过，API将在以后看到
if you want to migrate we have some
如果您想迁移，我们有一些
experimental limited support for a
实验性的有限支持
few of the rule types with Janet for you
珍妮特为您准备的几种规则类型
can this is kind of like spring boot but
可以像弹簧靴吗，但是
it's not at a naval rural migration
不是在海军农村迁移
support so if you annotated class with
支持，所以如果您用
that you get three extensions on the fly
您将获得三个扩展
external resource support which is
外部资源支持是
support for like temporary folder and
支持类似临时文件夹和
chain for a verifier support things like
验证者链支持诸如
air collectors in giant for and expected
巨大的空气收集器
exception support for well expected
对异常预期的异常支持
exception right so you can actually use
异常权限，因此您可以实际使用
these kind of rules with Jane and
简和
Jupiter because they map on to the UM
木星，因为它们映射到UM
the new extension API do we have yes and
新的扩展API，我们可以吗？
there wasn't mind a bug but it got
没有介意一个错误，但它得到了
released and fixed today and five and
今天发布并修复，还有五个
one so assertions yet we have a limited
一个这样的断言，但我们有一个局限性
corset I copied some of the basics from
紧身胸衣我复制了一些基础知识
Jane at 4 and then we rework some stuff
简在4岁时，我们再做一些工作
and expanded everything so we still got
并扩展了一切，所以我们仍然得到了
stuff like the sword equals of certain
像剑一样的东西肯定
unknown etcetera but every time you see
未知等等，但是每次看到
a green lambda can is that even green I
一个绿色的lambda罐子是什至绿色的我
don't know these are the laminate things
不知道这些是层压板的东西
that means you can use a lambda
这意味着您可以使用lambda
expression or a method reference with J
J的表达式或方法引用
and Jupiter so assert throws is the cool
和木星，所以断言是很酷的
new way to do expect exceptions assert
期待异常断言的新方法
timeout and assert panel timeout
超时和断言面板超时
preemptively there's to assert timeouts
抢先断言超时
like you might have timeout rule
就像你可能有超时规则
previously the difference is timeout
以前的区别是超时
will execute in the same thread and then
将在同一线程中执行，然后
stop after the test stops and tell you
测试停止后停止并告诉您
whether or not it finished in time the
是否及时完成
third time on primitive you will run
第三次在原始对象上运行
your code and a new thread and they'll
您的代码和新线程，他们将
kill it early preemptively right if it
如果可以的话，尽早杀死它吧
needs to I note on that is uh if using
我需要注意的是，如果使用
something like a framework like spring
像Spring这样的框架
that has transactional support where the
具有交易支持的地方
transaction context is tied to a thread
事务上下文绑定到线程
local for the current thread and you say
当前线程本地，你说
excerpt timeout primitively then Springs
摘录超时最初是Springs
transaction support would be broken and
交易支持将被破坏，
if you have other frameworks doing
如果您有其他框架在做
similar stuff you just need to keep that
类似的东西，你只需要保持
in mind so again time on potentially
请记住，因此再次可能
will end faster but it might break your
会更快结束，但可能会破坏您的
other framework code using I start all
其他框架代码使用我全部开始
this is what's known as inter assertions
这就是所谓的内部断言
or grouped assertions or something like
或分组的断言或类似的内容
what are they called
他们叫什么
soft assertions and sha right so you can
软断言和正确的权限，因此您可以
combine a bunch bunch together with end
将一束束与末端结合在一起
expressions and then Jana will report
表达式，然后Jana将报告
back all the failures instead of having
支持所有失败而不是
to rerun those tests another thing to
重新运行那些测试
point out is um the mess at the end now
指出现在是一团糟
so your message for why it failed since
所以你的信息为什么失败了
this should be an optional parameter
这应该是一个可选参数
comes it in in addition you can supply
另外它可以提供
your failure message as a supplier of
您作为供应商的失败信息
string with the lambda expression which
带有lambda表达式的字符串
means that if it takes a long time to
表示如果要花很长时间
compute it or maybe a long time but
计算它或可能很长时间，
there's no
没有
to generate error messages if the
生成错误消息，如果
surgeons don't fail right so that's why
外科医生不会失败，所以这就是为什么
we did that and if you want more power
我们做到了，如果您想获得更多动力
we're not forcing you to use our
我们不强迫您使用我们的
assertions if you don't want them feel
断言，如果您不希望他们感到
free to use a sergej hamcrest truth
免费使用sergej hamcrest真相
whatever right as long as those things
只要那些东西有权利
you're throwing assertion areas it's
你在抛出断言领域
gonna work fine with Jane and Jupiter
可以和简和木星一起工作
and with the platform as well so
和平台一样
assumptions has anyone ever used those
假设有人曾经使用过那些
in Jena for a few people right so you
在耶拿（Jena）有几个人，所以你
can say I assume this to be true and
可以说我认为这是真的，
otherwise don't execute the rest of the
否则不要执行其余的
test so we have a limited set of those
测试，所以我们只有有限的一组
taking over from J and 4 and that's for
从J和4接管，那是为了
aborting the test mid-flight it means
中途中止测试意味着
the test already started right the test
测试已经正确开始了
method is executing but you can say I
方法正在执行，但是你可以说我
check something in whoops I don't want
检查一些我不想要的东西
to continue and it won't market has
继续下去，它将不会有市场
failed I'll just say that it was skipped
失败，我只是说它被跳过了
otherwise if you want to actually skip
否则，如果您想实际跳过
it the whole thing I'm not even started
整个事情我都还没开始
then you could implement your own
那么你可以实现自己的
execution condition as we'll talk about
我们将讨论的执行条件
later on so we have stuff like assumed
后来，我们有一些假设
true assumed false to take boolean or
假设为true，则为false，表示布尔值或
boolean suppliers suppliers the strings
布尔供应商供应商字符串
for the messages etc and we have another
对于消息等，我们还有另一个
thing called assuming that it's kind of
所谓的假设是
a glorified if if you have an assumption
如果你有一个假设就荣耀
that passes the next few this code
通过下面的一些代码
otherwise don't and continue on with the
否则请不要继续
execution of the test method so this is
执行测试方法，所以这是
where I hope the demo gods are with me
我希望演示之神与我同在
all right all right so we have a
好吧好吧，所以我们有一个
wonderful calculator class it adds some
很棒的计算器类，它增加了一些
tracks multiplies divides and calculates
轨迹乘以除法并计算
Fibonacci Fibonacci could take a while
斐波那契斐波那契可能需要一段时间
hint maybe time outs you could divide by
提示也许超时可以除以
0 here right so you could have some kind
0在这里，所以你可以有一些
of errors the font
字体错误
basic text font edit 24 is gonna be huge
基本文本字体编辑24将会非常庞大
it knit so better yep okay cool
它编织得更好，是的，很酷
and yeah we have some cats people and
是的，我们有一些猫人，
stringy tools for calculating
严格的计算工具
palindromes so we have a test based on
回文，所以我们有一个基于
Janet for the instantiates the
珍妮特（Janet）实例化了
calculated substantive test uses the
计算的实质性测试使用
expected exception rule and the time
预期例外规则和时间
mount rule from JUnit 4 has some
JUnit 4的安装规则有一些
assertions I hope these are the right
断言我希望这些是正确的
ones yep they're all from Jane it for
是的，他们都是简的。
assert and then for exception testing
断言然后进行异常测试
right so it starts off saying none for
对，所以它开始不说
the expected exception and then for this
预期的异常，然后为此
particular case divided by zero says
特殊情况除以零表示
what it type it expects in the message
它在消息中期望的类型
and then does the thing that's supposed
然后做应该做的事情
to blow up and for timeouts absence I've
炸毁，超时我没有
commented out here so you could have
在这里评论掉了，所以你可以
done the old-school way like that where
像以前那样做旧派
you gonna done it with the global
你会与全球
timeout milliseconds a thousand so one
超时毫秒一千
second and then you execute the thing
第二，然后执行该事情
and see if it blows up so let's just run
看看它是否爆炸了，让我们运行
this test and see if it runs it does
这个测试，看看它是否运行
that's not too exciting what if we were
如果我们
to pick something bigger like that right
选择像这样的大东西
42 then that should hopefully blow up it
42那么那应该炸掉它
does and it gives us some kind of error
确实，这给了我们一些错误
something like test timed out after
像测试之后超时
thousand milliseconds so in January that
一月的毫秒数
does it preemptively there's no non
是否先发制人
pre-emptive mode for timeouts in jenefor
jenefor中的超时抢占模式
and for the exception if we expected or
除非我们期望
if we didn't
如果我们没有
and run that one then that would blow up
并运行那个然后会炸毁
with the exception right so it through
有例外的权利，所以它通过
the exception and now what we want to do
例外，现在我们要做什么
is you want to see how we can achieve
您是否想看看我们如何实现
the same stuff in Jane at five so this
简在五点钟的东西
is where the demo gods really might not
是演示之神可能真的没有的地方
be with me we'll give it a shot I'm
和我在一起我们会给我一个机会
gonna even typed the view big pide or
甚至会输入大视角
okay so now we have a new class right
好吧，现在我们有新班了
and what we're gonna do we're gonna say
我们要做什么我们要说
get rid of the J and for stuff except
除掉J和其他东西
the rules we'll leave those those there
我们会把那些人留在那里的规则
for a second alright so now it's
好一秒钟，现在是
complaining I'm gonna pick the test API
抱怨我要选择测试API
annotation from J and Jupiter right
来自J和木星的注释
I said things don't have to be public
我说过事情不必公开
she'll be able to delete all that clean
她将能够删除所有干净的
it up a little bit
一点点
no the assertions aren't there let me
没有断言没有让我
pick one of those from the right package
从正确的包装中选择其中之一
is that the right one it did from a
是它从
junior API surgeons so right now we've
初级API外科医生，所以现在我们已经
just converted the AHA so why is this
刚转换了AHA，这是为什么
failing anyone paying attention
没有任何人注意
the message is at the beginning that's
消息是在开头
what I'm saying right no longer at the
我说的对不对了
beginning so he put them at the end you
开始，所以他把它们放在最后
do it like that and if this were some
那样做，如果这是一些
kind of complex thing and you wanted to
有点复杂，你想
build it up well that's easy just make
很好地建立它，只需使
it a supplier like that so use a lambda
它是这样的供应商，所以要使用lambda
expression and that works nicely so if
表达式，效果很好，所以如果
we run this now what you're going to do
我们现在运行这个，你要做什么
that's divided by zero failed right we
除以零失败了吧，我们
expected that to happen and I mentioned
预计会发生，我提到
there's this rural migration support
有这种农村移民的支持
which supports the expected exception so
它支持预期的异常，所以
if I run it again now it's still divided
如果我现在再次运行它，它仍然分裂
by zero let's see what's going on here
零，让我们看看这里发生了什么
2905 a neighborhood migration you know
2905你知道的邻里迁移
expect exception none it should be in
期望没有异常，应该在
here right here with this expected
这里就在这里
exception support let me give that a
异常支持让我给一个
shot gun this is running right space
弹枪这是正确的空间
right to particular party oh that might
参加特定聚会的权利
have yes it's nice to have a an audience
是的，有一个观众很高兴
paying attention
注意
thank you very much see that that crowd
非常感谢你看到那群人
Juna for why does everything have to be
朱纳为什么要一切都必须
public yes so that's that's right but
公开是的，没错，但是
let's get rid of that right we don't we
让我们摆脱这种权利，我们不是
don't want to do that we're on a really
不想这样做，我们正在
migrate so now this thing doesn't exist
迁移，所以现在这个东西不存在
this is the air as well let you start
这也是空气，让您开始
like this assert throws and the type is
像这样断言抛出，类型是
that one and the thing we want to
那一个和我们想要的东西
execute is this so how do we surprise
这是执行，那么我们怎么惊讶
named expression like that alright so
这样命名的表达式好吧
far so good
到目前为止很好
if you run it now and save then that
如果您现在运行它并保存，那么
works alright and what if we haven't
一切正常，如果我们没有
checked the message well that's not too
检查消息很好，不是
difficult equals a lot equals expected
困难等于很多等于预期
who thinks that's going to work yep that
谁认为这行得通
works so this is how you do expected
有效，所以这就是您的预期
exceptions now in Jayne at 5 J and
Jayne现在5 J和
Jupiter and the last part to get rid of
木星和摆脱的最后一部分
is this this timeout thing so it was 42
这是这个超时的事情，所以是42
when it ended up being longer than we
当它比我们更长时
wanted and the timeouts not supported
想要和不支持超时
this in any way so we can just delete
可以通过任何方式删除
this and now if we run this this should
这个，现在，如果我们运行这个，这个应该
uh well it'll take a little bit of time
嗯，这需要一点时间
and we'll see how long it takes took
我们会花多长时间
over a second right so you want to make
在第二个权利，所以你想
sure that it doesn't take over a second
确保不会花费一秒钟
right and the way we do that is timeout
对，我们这样做的方式是超时
of Millie's for example a thousand
例如米莉的一千
so who thinks that's going to work it's
所以谁认为这行得通呢
going to say people can read this it
会说人们可以读懂它
says execution see the time out of 1,000
说执行看到时间超过了1,000
milliseconds by 390 so that was the
390毫秒，这是
non-preemptive one it let it run you can
非抢占式的它可以让它运行
see the whole the entire running time
查看整个运行时间
and what if we wanted to finish that we
如果我们想完成该怎么办
do that preemptively we could just say
先行地做到这一点，我们只能说
print of Lee and then we'll stop
李的照片，然后我们将停止
immediately after a second and give us
一秒钟后立即给我们
an error similar to what we saw in
与我们看到的类似的错误
jigging it for right so execution time
正确摆放它，以便执行时间
dot after 1000 milliseconds so that was
1000毫秒后点
instantaneous and by by the way if
顺便说一下，如果
you're wanting what this is this is just
你想知道这是什么
Java time duration of milliseconds of
Java持续时间（以毫秒为单位）
seconds and stuff like that so nice
秒之类的东西真好
little kind of linear path yep if you do
是的，有点线性路径
oh you mean do we kill it properly maybe
哦，你的意思是我们可能会正确杀死它吗
it attempts to it it might not do it in
它尝试它可能不会在
all cases if it's a really kind of
在所有情况下，如果真的是
rampant kind of thing we'll use an
猖ant的事情，我们将使用
executor service and we we do get the
遗嘱执行人服务，我们的确做到了
question was if it's going to run on
问题是它是否会继续
forever with the preemptively one of the
永远与先发制人之一
non one the non one no it will it will
非一个非一个没有它会
keep running it will run ever forever
继续运行它将永远运行
yes so if you know that it's something
是的，如果你知道那是什么
so if you want to time it you know it's
因此，如果您想计时，那就知道了
going to finish you just want to make
要完成，你只想做
sure it's not taking too long then you
确保不会花太长时间，然后您
could use a normal time on if you wanna
如果您想使用正常的时间
make sure that it's it might have some
确保它可能有一些
kind of infinite loop whatever you want
无限循环，随心所欲
to avoid that and kill it off you want
避免这种情况并杀死它
to do it preemptively but again the
抢先做，但再次
point there is you have to know if your
点，你必须知道你的
other framework code like spring or
其他框架代码，例如spring或
something he's using thread locals then
然后他正在使用线程局部变量
that wouldn't work so you'd have to
那是行不通的，所以你必须
figure out something but that's that's a
找出一些东西，但这就是
threading issue you have to to deal with
您必须处理的线程问题
anyway so I think that's it for the the
无论如何，我认为仅此而已
basics on that okay all right so tagging
没关系的基础知识，所以标记
mm-hmm we've been going right so we have
嗯，我们一直往前走，所以我们有
an out tagging tation you can clear on
您可以清除的标记外标签
interface class or method something like
接口类或方法类似
this add tag fast on a test method my
这个添加标签快速测试方法我
fast test and by default all the tags
快速测试，默认情况下所有标签
are enabled so it doesn't actually have
已启用，因此实际上并没有
any
任何
any input or any impact on the running
任何输入或对运行的任何影响
test plan you'd have to actually specify
您必须实际指定的测试计划
to include tags or explicitly exclude
包括标签或明确排除
tags otherwise the tags or are ignored
标签，否则标签或被忽略
so you can come up with custom tags
所以你可以拿出自定义标签
because we support mid annotations right
因为我们支持中间注释
just declare add tag adds a meta
只是声明添加标签添加一个元
annotation so meta annotation means
注释，因此元注释意味着
annotation declared on top of another
在另一个顶部声明的注释
annotation in the source code so here we
源代码中的注释，所以在这里我们
have our own annotation named fast and
有我们自己的注释，名为fast和
it is annotated with that tag fast and
它使用该标签快速注释，
it can be used on methods and it's
它可以用在方法上
retained at runtime so then we could
保留在运行时，这样我们就可以
rewrite the previous slide like this
像这样重写上一张幻灯片
fast test and you agreed reuse the fast
快速测试，您同意快速重复使用
tag across your codebase if you want to
如果要在代码库中标记
go one step further you can compose tags
更进一步，您可以撰写标签
a very cool feature very popular in
一个非常酷的功能，在
spring and now possible with with j-unit
春天，现在可以用j-unit
so you can Eclair tag is meditation with
这样你就可以将Eclair标记与
other annotations they could be other
其他注释可能是其他
annotations from Jaina or as I do in the
来自吉安娜（Jaina）或我在
spring testing sport I combined spring
春季测试运动我结合弹簧
annotations and Jade annotations to
注释和Jade注释
really simplify the configuration so
确实简化了配置，所以
here we see a combination of tag fast
在这里，我们看到了快速标记组合
and test from Jane and Jupiter and this
并从简和木星进行测试
is a fast test so we can just rewrite
是一个快速测试，所以我们可以重写
that last one as at fast test and you
最后一个是快速测试，而您
might have integration test smoke tests
可能有集成测试烟雾测试
different kind of things like that and
诸如此类的不同事物
again you can also combine this with
同样，您也可以将其与
spring support for transactional SQL
弹簧支持事务性SQL
scripts and stuff like that so pretty
脚本之类的东西真漂亮
powerful stuff test names so by default
功能强大的东西测试名称，因此默认情况下
defaults to the class name or the method
默认为类名或方法
name is you're familiar with with things
名字是你熟悉的东西
like testing G&amp;J and it for etc so the
例如测试G＆J及其它，等等
characters not limited on the Java
Java上不限制的字符
syntax but we have at display name and J
语法，但显示名称和J
and Jupiter laws you have a custom
和木星定律，你有一个习惯
display name can contain spaces special
显示名称可以包含特殊空格
characters and even emoji yes so some
人物甚至表情符号是的，所以有些
guy complained on the internet and the
家伙在互联网上抱怨
Twittersphere that it was stupid that we
我们愚蠢的Twittersphere
have support from oh geez and I had to
有哦geez的支持，我不得不
say well we didn't actually aim to
说的好，我们实际上并非旨在
support support emojis we wanted to
我们想要支持的支持表情符号
support the first two special characters
支持前两个特殊字符
and spaces and stuff like that and then
和空间之类的东西，然后
one day I was like when if we can
有一天，我想如果可以的话
actually use an emoji in there that's a
实际上在其中使用表情符号
character right and it works we didn't
正确的字符，我们没有
aim to but it works I'll show you so
旨在但确实有效，我会告诉你
anyway
无论如何
dependency injection this is where the
依赖注入这是
extension model meets the programming
扩展模型满足编程要求
model also like to say so we have a
模特也想说，所以我们有一个
parameter resolver extension API this is
参数解析器扩展API，这是
somewhat analogous to spring MVC support
有点类似于Spring MVC支持
for argument resolvers and stuff like
用于参数解析器之类的东西
that resolves a parameter as you might
可以解析参数
guess either for a constructor or a
猜测是构造函数还是
method
方法
and not just for test methods and
而不仅仅是测试方法
lifecycle methods but also yeah for
生命周期方法，但也是
constructors so you can register
构造函数，以便您可以注册
multiple simultaneously they compete but
他们同时竞争多个，但
only one wins because ask you if they
只有一个赢，因为问你是否
support it and use cases stuff like
支持它并使用案例之类的东西
injecting a server URL a data source if
如果有，则将服务器URL注入数据源
you have connection to a database a
您已连接到数据库
spring application context to example
Spring应用程序上下文示例
stuff like that so or mocs has another
诸如此类的东西或Mocs还有另一个
another popular one test invoke this out
另一个流行的测试将其调用
of the box you can inject this into
您可以将其注入
constructor test before each etc from J
构造函数在每个J等进行测试之前
and Jupiter gives you access to the
木星可以让您访问
display name tags class meth and stuff
显示名称标签类meth和东西
like that we have our own parameters all
这样我们都有自己的参数
were registered automatically behind the
被自动注册在
scenes that's what we say eating our own
这就是我们说吃自己的场景
dog food that was actually a design
狗粮实际上是一种设计
principle we had for the whole the whole
我们整体的原则
Jane 2:5 effort is that if we have an
简2：5的努力是，如果我们有一个
extension point or something we want to
扩展点或我们想要的东西
implement then we create an essential
实施，然后我们创建一个必要的
point for it we have to bend it lift
为此，我们必须将其弯曲
that and other people can also implement
和其他人也可以实施
the same extension point so see also for
相同的扩展点，因此也请参见
using your PT test you can use on have
使用您的PT测试，您可以在
repetition info injected you can have a
插入重复信息，您可以
test reporter injected to create some
测试记者注入创建一些
additional test reporting information
其他测试报告信息
the maketo extension is something we've
maketo扩展名是我们
implemented as a sample and Makua teams
作为示例和Makua团队实施
taken over I wrote the spring extension
接手我写了春天的延伸
and that's been released in spring 5
并且已经在 spring 5发布了
we'll see that that later on so next up
我们稍后会看到
live coding tags display names in a pin
实时编码标签在大头针中显示名称
see injection what do we have here so I
看注射我们在这里有什么所以我
have a junior 5 tests you know I'd like
有一个初中5次测试，你知道我想要
to make this a test it's a test
做一个测试，这是一个测试
I would like to tag it with fast now
我现在想用快速标记
it's a fast test
这是一个快速的测试
licky call this slow or normal or
licky称这缓慢或正常，或
doesn't really matter so now if I just
其实并不重要，所以如果我现在
run this they're both going to run two
运行这个，他们都将运行两个
tests one normally fast that's because
测试一个通常快的是因为
we didn't specify any tags right I said
我说的我们没有指定任何标签
by default everything's included so if
默认情况下，所有内容都包括在内
in Eclipse I go to the run
在Eclipse中，我开始运行
configurations and arguments Eclipse
Eclipse的配置和参数
four seven one eight that's support for
四七一八的支持
this you can say include tag fast like
您可以说快速包含标签
that and run and then we should see ha
那并运行，然后我们应该看到哈
ha now it only ran one test which was in
哈现在它只进行了一项测试
fact the fast test right so you can come
事实上，快速测试是正确的，所以你可以来
do this within Eclipse I'm not sure if
在Eclipse中执行此操作，我不确定是否
you can get IntelliJ yet so you can do
您可以获得IntelliJ，因此您可以
this from your your Gradle build and
这是从您的Gradle版本开始的，
from your maven build and also with the
从您的Maven构建以及
console launcher so that stuff works
控制台启动器，以便工作
like that
像那样
now again I mentioned you might want to
现在我再次提到你可能想要
create something like fast test I've
创建类似我已经进行的快速测试
already written it for you here's this
已经为你写了这是这个
has tag tag ves fast and tests can be
拥有标签ves ves快速，测试可以
used on methods retaining runtime so I
用于保留运行时的方法，所以我
should be able to replace that get rid
应该能够取代那摆脱
of that
在那
rerun the tests and we see that again
重新运行测试，我们再次看到
that one was actually run the fast test
那个实际上是在进行快速测试
so this is this cool custom annotation
这就是这个很棒的自定义注解
combining tag and test and I mentioned
结合标签和测试，我提到
you can also get information like the
您还可以获取诸如
dependency injection so you can say I'd
依赖注入，所以你可以说我会
like that please give it to me and just
这样，请给我，只是
for fun I'll just print it out all right
为了好玩，我会把它打印出来
so what kind of nope small team right so
那什么样的小团队呢？
now if we run that lets you see some
现在，如果我们运行它，您可以看到一些
stuff the console we see the display
填充控制台，我们看到了显示
name was this fast test tags yep that's
这个快速测试标签的名称是
there this is the class that we're
这是我们的班级
running in here's the test method that
在这里运行的测试方法
we were in right so we get his kind
我们是对的，所以我们得到了他的帮助
information but the display name was
信息，但显示名称为
what was that it was the name of the
那是什么名字
method with the parameter list so what
参数列表的方法是什么
if we wanted to have something custom
如果我们想定制一些东西
display name fast tests with some
显示名称与一些快速测试
special characters now we see that's
现在我们看到特殊字符
included here in the information but
包含在信息中，但
also more importantly here fast test
更重要的是这里的快速测试
so right see that fast test yes cool and
好吧，看到快速测试是很酷的，
now this is where I have to go back and
现在这是我必须回去的地方
copy from somewhere you cannot type
从无法键入的地方复制
emoji in Eclipse I don't know why but
Eclipse中的表情符号，我不知道为什么，但是
you can copy and paste them in so what's
您可以将其复制并粘贴到其中
gonna happen now this is where I get the
会发生现在这是我得到的地方
biggest applause I guarantee it
最大的掌声我保证
there it's in the reporting whoo-hoo but
在报告中，哇，但是
you didn't even see it in the display
你甚至没有在显示屏上看到它
yet okay now that's the cool part Oh yep
好吧，现在这是最酷的部分
there it is and if we were to run it
在那里，如果我们要运行它
from the command line nope what am i
从命令行不，我是什么
doing
在做
where am i this is not the fun I had
我在哪里，这不是我的乐趣
before I have a Gradle build with the
在我使用Gradle构建之前
plug-in it's gonna output a tree of the
插件会输出一个
results in theory there it was and Wow
理论上的结果是，哇
so very very cool stuff there okay
所以那里的东西非常非常好
that's what you all came for emoji so
那就是你们所有人都想要的表情符号
yeah you're welcome
是的，不客气
oh no I hit that favor the wrong place
哦，不，我撞到了那个错误的地方
somewhere oh my goodness
哦，我的天哪
pretty good okay we saw that stuff all
很好，我们看到了所有的东西
right moving on I got to go fast now so
继续前进，我现在必须快走
if you have more questions and stuff
如果您还有其他问题
we'll covered it in the buff tonight so
今晚我们会用buff覆盖它
conditional test execution heights this
有条件的测试执行高度
is a game-changer right this is inspired
是改变游戏规则的灵感来源
by like the fact there was ignoring Jada
就像事实是忽略贾达
for and then on spring we had support
因为然后在春天，我们得到了支持
for if profile value and spring out
如果配置文件值和弹出
support for things like conditions and
支持诸如条件和
profiles and stuff like that so that'd
个人资料之类的东西，所以
be really cool without also exists in
真的很酷，没有也存在
Janet we have an execution addition
珍妮特（Janet）
condition without you can implement at
条件，如果您无法实施
disable is the first one I implemented
禁用是我实施的第一个
for that and there's a disabled
为此，有一个残疾人
condition that actually supports that
实际支持的条件
you can check out the code for it and
您可以签出代码，
like I said this is a game changer
就像我说的这是改变游戏规则的人
because it's not only something we do
因为这不仅是我们要做的
and Jana you can write your own and
和Jana，您可以编写自己的
people do and I really think that's
人们这样做，我真的认为那是
gonna be a very popular feature so why
将会是一个非常受欢迎的功能，为什么
might you want to do that you might want
你可能想做你想做的
to do it based on the current OS with a
在当前操作系统的基础上使用
current Java version or the current day
当前Java版本或当前日期
or something like that different
或类似的东西
different ideas system property
不同的想法系统属性
environment variable these kind of
这些环境变量
things you can just write your own
你可以自己写的东西
conditions and then share that across
条件，然后将其共享
your codebase and there will be some
您的代码库，会有一些
other projects that are implementing
正在实施的其他项目
stuff like that I've done some cool
像这样的东西我做得很酷
support and spring for that as well
支持和为此
so you can deactivate these things if
因此您可以在以下情况下停用这些功能
you want to see maybe maybe our tests
你想看看也许我们的测试
are still working or working now that
现在仍在工作或正在工作
we're disabled maybe they were broken
我们被禁用了，也许他们坏了
maybe they work now you can disable that
也许他们现在可以工作了，您可以禁用该功能
by saying June conditions to activate
说出6月的激活条件
and the name of the condition where the
以及条件的名称
package and a pattern is so like that so
包装和图案是如此
you mix this here run all the tests that
您将其混合在此处运行所有测试
maybe we're broken before cool features
也许我们在炫酷功能之前就被打破了
like that so next up default methods
这样，接下来的默认方法
mm-hmm so eight right introduce the
嗯，嗯，所以八对介绍
concept of test interface basically an
测试界面的概念基本上是
NJ and Jupiter so you can have basically
新泽西和木星，所以你基本上可以
multiple inheritance and tests aka
多重继承和测试
testing traits you can use bunch of the
测试特征，您可以使用一堆
annotations in on default methods like
默认方法中的注释
before all in after all but caveat here
毕竟毕竟，但要注意这里
only if you're using this at test
仅当您在测试中使用它时
instance lifecycle per class otherwise
否则每个类的实例生命周期
those methods have to be static before
这些方法必须是静态的
each after each test these different
每次测试后这些都不一样
variations tags extend with all this
变体标签扩展了所有这些
kind of stuff can be included in those
那些东西可以包括在那些
test interfaces so to speak so we have
可以这么说测试接口
one I'll quickly show you string tests
我将快速向您展示字符串测试
if I were to run that there are no test
如果我要跑步，那就没有测试
methods here do you see any tests no but
您在这里看到的任何测试方法
it has tests so where do they come from
它有测试，所以它们来自哪里
well we can double click they come from
好吧，我们可以双击它们来自
default methods and interfaces so here
默认方法和接口，所以在这里
we have a comfortable contract and
我们有一个舒适的合同，
equals contract and stuff like that so
等于合同之类的东西
you can have reusable contracts or
您可以拥有可重复使用的合同，或者
testing traits and implement them
测试特质并实施它们
implement them in your test classes
在测试类中实现它们
that's kind of the point there okay next
接下来就是重点了
up Nessun test classes so in j and
所以在j和
afford there are two runners than you
负担得起比你多两个跑步者
know of custom runners in the world that
知道世界上的自定义跑步者
allowed support for this basically
基本上允许对此提供支持
enables on logical hierarchical grouping
启用逻辑层次分组
of your test classes with sheridan's
谢里丹的考试课程
initialization state from outer
外部的初始化状态
instances and you do this without
实例，而您无需
clearing that nested on a non-static
清除嵌套在非静态上的
nested class also known as an inner
嵌套类也称为内部
class right and you can even combine on
上课权利，你甚至可以结合
nested classes and in test interfaces we
嵌套类和测试接口中
can see the testing a stack example
可以看到测试堆栈的例子
which is a cool one in the user guide as
这在用户指南中很酷
well testing a stock demo so if we look
好测试一个股票演示，所以如果我们看
in here we see it makes use of um
在这里，我们看到它利用了um
display name and it has this nested
显示名称，它具有此嵌套
class class here right and then it has
在这里上课，然后有
its own tests in there and then wait oh
在里面自己测试，然后等待哦
there's even more nesting so what is
还有更多的嵌套，那是什么
this going to look like when we run it
这看起来像当我们运行它时
it's kind of a BDD style right so now if
现在有点像BDD风格
I look on this expand all and zoom in
我看这全部展开并放大
then we see cool stuff like that right
然后我们看到像这样的好东西
so you have the very various levels
所以你有很多不同的水平
there the various test methods and the
那里有各种测试方法和
classes and with use of that display
类以及使用该显示
name you can have custom names having
您可以使用具有以下名称的自定义名称
more kind of BDD style so that's a cool
更加BDD风格，这很酷
new feature as well
以及新功能
okay repeated tests you just say at
好的重复测试，你只是在说
repeated tests specify the number you
重复测试指定您的号码
can have the repetition info injected if
可以注入重复信息，如果
you want override the custom display now
您要立即覆盖自定义显示
if you want it would look something like
如果你想它看起来像
this I repeat it has five do it five
我再说一遍，它有五个做到了
times you can even change the name as I
你甚至可以像我一样更改名字
mentioned so if your here's an example
提到所以如果你这是一个例子
in German if you wanted to change it to
如果您想将其更改为德语
say instead of repetition one of two you
说而不是重复两个你之一
could say Peter Hold'em eins quince why
可以说Peter Hold'em了为什么
if you speak German something like that
如果你会说德语
so different languages change stuff like
所以不同的语言会改变诸如
that priming our chests much better than
那使我们的胸部变得更好
what we had in Jay at four so you just
我们四点钟在周杰伦遇到的一切
use a parametrized test instead of test
使用参数化测试代替测试
specify the source of arguments sources
指定参数来源
we have lots of things there check out
我们有很多东西可以结帐
the user guide for that so we have value
用户指南，因此我们很有价值
source for just straight values strings
直接值字符串的来源
etc enum source for getting enum
等获取枚举的枚举源
constants method source so you can
常量方法源，因此您可以
actually delegate to a method static
实际上委托给静态方法
method that serves as a factory for your
可以作为您工厂的方法
arguments also support for CSV inline in
参数还支持CSV内联
the annotation also from the file system
注释也来自文件系统
or you can have our argument source and
或者你可以有我们的论点来源和
clincher and custom arguments provider
敲定和自定义参数提供程序
so for conversion implicit conversion
所以对于转换隐式转换
for most basic types genomes Java x
适用于大多数基本类型的基因组Java x
stuff like that you can also have
这样的东西你也可以
explicit conversion if you implement
如果实现，则进行显式转换
these API is here premier HSN actually
这些API实际上是这里的首要HSN
would look something like this so add
看起来像这样，所以添加
parameterize test value source list of
参数化测试值来源列表
strings here an array so these things
在这里字符串数组这样的事情
are palindromes read them forward and
回文是向前读吗？
backward they work and this test passes
向后他们工作，并且此测试通过
it's in the example code which I can
在示例代码中，我可以
show more tonight or you can check out
今晚显示更多，或者您可以退房
online I have a link later so dynamic
网上我以后有一个链接这么动态
tests this is a normally static write
测试这是正常的静态写入
known at compile time with that test but
该测试在编译时已知，但
a dynamic test is registered at runtime
动态测试在运行时注册
with a lambda expression an attendent
带着lambda表情参加
method with that test Factory and we
该测试工厂的方法，我们
have some different ways to do that so
有一些不同的方法可以做到这一点
basically as you say is at test Factory
基本上就像你说的是在测试工厂
and you return a stream of a dynamic
然后返回动态流
test or a collection list something like
测试或收集列表，例如
that and then you just create to your
然后，您只需创建自己的
stream you build it all up dynamically
流式传输，您可以动态构建所有内容
however you want to programmatically
但是你想以编程方式
conditionally etc here we're saying
有条件等我们在这里说
first ten even integers so start with
前十个偶数整数，所以从
zero n equals n plus two get the first
零n等于n加2得到第一个
ten take each number and create a
十取每个数字并创建一个
dynamic test out of that so that's a
动态测试，所以这是一个
static factory from the dynamic test
静态工厂从动态测试
class and we're giving it a name so test
课，我们给它起一个名字，所以测试
in that be tested zero blah blah blah
在那被测试的零等等等等
and then assert true performance urgent
然后断言真正的表现很紧急
so you can do super dynamic stuff you
所以你可以做超级动态的东西
can also have containers and si
也可以有容器和si
containers as well if you want
容器也可以
so I will probably demo that tonight
所以今晚我可能会演示
what's missing scenario tests we like to
我们想缺少什么场景测试
bring that in and one of the future
带入未来
releases ordering you can't currently
发布您当前无法订购的订单
order the test methods or stuff like
订购测试方法或类似的东西
that knows no support yet for parallel
尚不支持并行
execution within the framework itself
在框架本身中执行
there might be support for example in
可能会有例如
and may even surefire but that's outside
甚至可能会确保生火，但这在外面
the platform execution and user-defined
平台执行和用户定义
thread maybe for GUI based stuff we
线程可能针对基于GUI的东西
don't have that in yet and declared of
还没有，并宣布
test suites for the Jaina platform we
用于Jaina平台的测试套件
have the support for test Suites using
支持使用以下内容的测试套件
the Jain it for platform runner if you
如果您是Jain的平台跑步者
want to do that but not for the platform
想要这样做但不适合平台
itself
本身
that's a generic way and as I mentioned
这是一种通用的方式，正如我提到的
before it's a Java 9 module path
在成为Java 9模块路径之前
scanning we'll be adding in soon as well
扫描，我们也会尽快添加
so I'm gonna just briefly talk about
所以我只是简单地谈谈
this their support in spring since
这是他们在春天以来的支持
Spring Framework 500 released when who
Spring Framework 500发布时间
knows the back of that guy I'm sure he
我知道那个家伙的背
knows last week right
知道上周吧
so supports all the core testing
因此支持所有核心测试
integration support in spring plus
Spring Plus中的集成支持
support for dependency injection for
支持依赖注入
constructors and methods also super cool
构造函数和方法也很酷
conditional test execution via spell
通过咒语有条件地执行测试
expressions so dynamic load expressions
表达式，所以动态负载表达式
also works with spring for just a
也可以和spring一起使用
project in my github repository if you
如果您在我的github仓库中的项目
want to try out Jaina 5 on spring 4 and
想在春季4尝试吉安娜5，并且
you're not on on spring 5 yet so there's
您还没有在5年春季参加，所以
a spring extension for that
春天的延伸
simplification with med annotations
使用med注释简化
spring Jane and config and spring Jane
春天简和配置和春天简
it web.config and then these enabled if
它web.config，然后启用这些
and disabled if annotations so I will
并禁用，如果注释，所以我会
have to show those during the buff I
必须在抛光期间显示那些
think I just want to point out as well
想我也想指出
spring boot also works with Jane at 5 so
spring boot 也可以在5点钟与Jane合作
you just say at spring be test and
你只是说在春天做测试
extend with the spring annotation so we
用spring注释扩展，所以我们
have an example here
这里有一个例子
please use Jane and Jupiter with spring
请在春季使用简和木星
and you spring boot test other stuff
然后你用弹簧靴测试其他东西
from spring boot stuff from spring
来自春季的靴子来自春季的靴子
create a custom annotation and then I
创建一个自定义注释，然后我
can use it super short like this this
可以像这样超级短
comes from an example app I have all
来自我拥有的所有示例应用程序
that configuration one annotation my
该配置一个注释我
events controller tests custom display
事件控制器测试自定义显示
name auto wiring in the mock MVC that's
在模拟MVC中命名自动接线
automatically created by spring boot and
由Spring Boot自动创建并
then using spring mocking me see for
然后用春天嘲笑我看到
testing so in closing lots information
测试，以便在平仓信息中
on the web start off at JDI org check
在Web上从JDI org开始检查
out the user guide check out the
查阅用户指南，查看
reference manual
参考手册
Javadoc etc feedback get ur github Stack
Javadoc等反馈获取您的github堆栈
Overflow spring resources
溢泉资源
as I mentioned please come tonight to
正如我提到的，请今晚到
the Boff and there's also another talk
鲍夫，还有另一个话题
tomorrow more about extensibility and
明天更多关于可扩展性和
this is the demo so that was that was it
这是演示，仅此而已
for the roving tour I'll be out
为了巡回演出，我会出去
afterwards for questions and also at the
之后提出问题，并在
off tonight so thanks for coming
今晚下班，谢谢您的光临
[Applause]
[掌声]